Scientific train will remove I have bought
such nice clothes for your birthday
what should I tell you Premo love you need a little I am
very tensed in Mumbai right now that I am
talking about marriage and they don't listen so
I sleep with them Ujjaini
people sleep like this this guy is listening so intently that if
Shraddha Prem and your wife and sister-in-law
both get trapped in a lion's cage then who will
save you Premo is this something to ask
in the office I will save the city I
am here Aries brother I am saying if you get married then you will
sleep like this
[praise]
then it gets intense sir you have kids too
send me the channel tell me I will deal with the girl
because little Remo I
want to stay in your heart forever Rambo Rambo
but don't fight with other girls
why are you not getting married
tell me quickly I don't have anything to do with anything
problem there is a baba
in Uttarakhand his name is Varun
Bune no comment
[praise]
hey there is only one  The
head teacher was this, he was with Vishwa Kanya, ah, what happened to
me, right now your tension is there, if you have any
problem with your team sir, tell me what is your problem, it would be a good
thing, no, if anyone has a problem with Little, that the
result is like last year,
Shraddha, you
can break my heart and see the books once again
[Praise]
I, someone stop this man, someone, ah,
listen, from your lap, this is the result,
what do you want to judge
Dharmesh about, I will do it after this,
[Praise]
Oh my love, someone stop this man, something happened to me,
Irfan, tell me,
where are you in the Vrindavan trap,
look at me, I will make every body,
give me two-and-a-half years,
and Varun has given a lot of details in London,
look, look, the song, the intimate part about landing, will you leave it in London, please, please, I am
folding my hands, whatever landing happens, we will leave it in London, on this
I know a baba
who has married thrice,
yes, yes
[Music], he
threw it from the fastest, 25
Teghra has come out on the road
that the wind and the heat wave Welcome Welcome Welcome to
India Welcome to India this man is published in the newspaper I don't even know I don't know
and from where he is taken out
so I am the first one who should do
Shraddha
that ah ah Krishna
torch off that unfaithful a little difficult
romantic role I ca
n't even imagine I am
coming under this factory I oh God this played played played played
you are crazy and Raghav
Raghav this is different and neither I am not
and tell me sir what has happened this has happened
tradition prestige and discipline wickets are left
neither I follow it nor let
my children do it it happened that
Welcome to India team
[praise]
Jhaal Raghu Bhaiya give humor by the way you have
grown up the find out confusion if you do one more then it will be a
problem friend one should be very suspicious
show that lovers don't die they survive
[music]
stay on 163 I will swear
that ah
that Pratap ah you very-very have the power of
view on
children come here na
if  I am telling you with guarantee
that till date you would not have seen this dance that is
Kar Do
because we have not shown it yet.
[Praise]
secondly, it is still of both of you, there is nothing like that
and love you love you love you
[Music]
so come on you talk
pak pak pak pak pak also what is this what is this
please tell
Ajay, the
children who see the
true ones in the mind, the
stars in the eyes of the whole world and counting the stars in your memory,
Mehta stays awake the whole night etc., one has to
move to the other side but which will happen now
after which all the three captains
get up from the narrow lane and run away thinking that
you will fly away from there, you will
give me your faces, reduce me